<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>camsinko.net</title><link>https://camsinko.net/</link><description>Recent content on camsinko.net</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 01:04:47 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://camsinko.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Danger of Single Industry Cities</title><link>https://camsinko.net/posts/the-danger-of-single-industry-cities/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 01:04:47 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://camsinko.net/posts/the-danger-of-single-industry-cities/</guid><description>The Rubber Capital of the World Origin and Growth in the early 1900s, cars are brought to market and changed America forever. My home town of Akron, Ohio became the epicenter for tire production, a critical wear-item for cars. Akron quickly became a boomtown, exploding in population 5x from about 40 thousand in 1900 to over 200 thousand by 1920. This sort of growth isn&amp;rsquo;t even seen anymore in present-day America.</description></item><item><title>Words I Live By</title><link>https://camsinko.net/posts/words-i-live-by/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 18:35:22 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://camsinko.net/posts/words-i-live-by/</guid><description>Surrender to the Flow There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of things we can&amp;rsquo;t control. The weather, traffic, politics, etc. Rather than let these bother me, I aim to focus on the things I can control.
Origin: Phish - The Lizards Money Beats Soul You know how much your soul&amp;rsquo;s worth?
Your soul&amp;rsquo;s worth about as much as you can get on Wall Street, my dear
— Jim Morrison1
It&amp;rsquo;s a rather unfortunate fact.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://camsinko.net/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://camsinko.net/about/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been fascinated with computers for as long as I can remember. It started with VB scripts, then evolved to Java and Python, then Linux and C. I&amp;rsquo;ve come to learn that I simply love designing with quality tools, and computers are the most powerful tools of today. I especially like writing software for electronics, networking, and hands-on projects.
Born in Akron, Ohio in 1997, i&amp;rsquo;m one of the oldest of Gen Z and grew up in The Rust Belt.</description></item><item><title>Stuff</title><link>https://camsinko.net/stuff/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://camsinko.net/stuff/</guid><description>Hardware Laptop: MacBook Air M1 in Rose Gold. Why Rose Gold? Because gold is bold, like that sweet, sweet M1.
Phone: iPhone 12 Pro Max. Was rocking Android for years, but don&amp;rsquo;t got time to be messing around with ROMs anymore. The beauty of the Apple ecosystem, it just works. I chose the 12 Pro Max to circumvent the need to buy a nice camera.
Keyboard: Realforce 87U Topre Keyboard with variable actuation weights.</description></item></channel></rss>